[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 16]
Mrs. Zhou,
aren't these clothes your family's?
How are they so messed up?
You're really careless.
[Photo Studio]
Take a seat here.
We'd like to order.
Shrimp with green peas.
Stir-fried eel shreds.
Sliced pork with egg white.
Maybe order less.
It's just the two of us.
So pricey to eat here.
Don't worry.
Double sesame flaky pastry.
Plus a white fungus
and fruit dessert soup.
Serve them now.
Okay.
Thank you.
I haven't played
the host properly during your stay here.
You keep treating me to meals.
How are you the host now?
We're both from Tiecheng.
Fang.
I'm going back tomorrow.
So I figured I should
treat you to a proper dinner
before departure.
I rarely go on business trips.
Who knows
when we will see each other next time.
But rest assured.
I'll definitely come visit you
when I have time.
I'd like to go to a specialty store to buy
some local treats
for my co-workers tomorrow.
Shall we go together?
I'm tied up tomorrow.
Well then...
My train leaves at 8:30 tomorrow.
Will you come see me off?
I wish you a safe journey.
Let go!
Let go.
What's going on?
Why are you fighting again?
Let go, both of you.
Let go!
Can the two of you just stop fighting?
As the older sister, can't you go easy
on your little brother?
And you. Why do you have to fight
your sister over everything?
What have you learned at school?
Respect the old
and care for the young, okay? Come on.
I didn't get it again.
Go in the room.
No more fighting.
Go inside.
Hao Fang,
bring the clothes in.
It's going to rain.
Mrs. Zhou,
when did you start smoking?
Aren't you afraid your husband will mind?
I get mad...
just at the sight of your wife.
She's really infuriating.
What happened?
"What happened?"
I told her not to wash her hair so often,
but she just did it again.
Is her hair so dirty
that she has to wash it every day?
The water for washing hair costs money,
doesn't it?
I get it now.
You get it?
Only you would fancy her. You see,
someone introduced a girl to you
a long time ago.
She was pretty
and had a lot going for her.
Yet you didn't like her.
Keep it down.
Others could hear you.
"Keep it down?"
Even all the neighbors know.
I've been saying it for years.
Can your wife speak Shanghainese?
No.
She doesn't even understand it till now.
Enough said. Stop it.
"Enough said."
All you do is paper over things with me.
All my years of raising you meant nothing.
♪ Your image from yesterday
is still before my eyes ♪
♪ The laughter from yesterday
still rings in my ears ♪
♪ Years drift away in silence ♪
♪ The warmth in my heart never fades ♪
♪ I'll follow you to the edge of the sky ♪
♪ Hand in hand until the end of time ♪
♪ Along the path
that the years have left behind ♪
♪ We shall meet again
in the mist-like yesterday ♪
♪ I'll follow you to the edge of the sky ♪
♪ Hand in hand until the end of time ♪
♪ Along the path
that the years have left behind ♪
♪ We shall meet again
in the mist-like yesterday ♪
♪ Faces change and years pass ♪
♪ The warmth in my heart never fades ♪
♪ I'll follow you to the edge of the sky ♪
Fang,
go with me.
I know I'm silly.
You told me the ancient story
of Wei Sheng holding the pillar.
♪ We shall meet again
in the mist-like yesterday ♪
I think I'm just like Weisheng.
I don't want to be apart from you.
When I'm back home, I'll get a divorce
and tell my wife everything.
♪ I'll follow you to the edge of the sky ♪
I got paid less
than the previous month again.
People pick on me every day.
This is so annoying.
What an expensive spread today.
♪ We shall meet again
in the mist-like yesterday ♪
Three dishes and a soup.
You knew I received my salary
today, right?
Here, put it away.
I have something to tell you.
♪ Along the path
that the years have left behind ♪
What do you mean by that?
Are you out of your mind?
You want a divorce?
Let's go for it then.
♪ We shall meet again
in the mist-like yesterday ♪
You think I'd fear you?
Don't ever come back
if you have the guts!
If you are leaving,
take both kids with you!
Director,
you are Weiguo's supervisor.
Please be the judge.
[Production Pioneer
and Quality Model Worker]
My husband Weiguo took a trip to Shanghai
and came back a big shot.
He asked for a divorce
the moment he reached home,
saying that he doesn't love me at all
and that his heart
belongs to someone else.
Director, I just want to ask you
[Production Pioneer
and Quality Model Worker]
if all the men who have been to Shanghai
behave like that.
What's it about now?
Are the women there prettier
and more stylish
than those in Tiecheng?
Comrade Guo,
please calm down.
Sit down and let's talk.
Director,
I know
he made a mistake and that he is guilty.
He has failed the organization
after all these years of nurturing.
But he is just confused.
He is by no means a bad person.
He simply lost his head.
That woman seduced him.
She knew he had a family,
yet she still threw herself at him.
Isn't it a matter of ideological conduct,
and a case of corrupting
the working class?
Today, I came to your office
not because I wanted to destroy him.
I meant to beg the organization
to save him
and our little family.
Our kids are too young.
I can't let them grow up feeling ashamed.
The exit is over there.
Walk straight ahead.
It's too high, isn't it?
Keep moving inside. Mind your safety.
Do you feel cold?
Come on.
Have your mouth covered.
Don't run around. Come here, Hao Peng.
Watch your step.
Keep moving inside. Mind your safety.